tmb.in 2013-05-14

# Privacy Policy - Click Here To See Our Privacy Policy : Get the Best Interest Rates on Deposits from the Best Indian Bank for NRI Deposits

[Home](http://www.tmb.in/best_interest_rates/best_indian_bank_offering_high_interest_rates_for_nri_deposits.html "best indian bank offering high interest rates for nri deposits")[Helpdesk](http://www.tmb.in/helpdesk/customer_service_and_support_resources.html "customer service and support resources")[Policies & Disclosures](http://www.tmb.in/policy_statutory_norms/our_statutory_polices_and_disclosures.html "our statutory polices and disclosures")Privacy Policy

###### click here to see our privacy policy

In the course of using this website [www.tmb.in] or availing the products and services vide the online application forms and questionnaires, Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd and its Affiliates may become privy to the personal information of its customers, including information that is of a confidential nature.

Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and has taken all necessary and reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of the customer information and its transmission through the world wide web and it shall not be held liable for disclosure of the confidential information when in accordance with this Privacy Commitment or in terms of the agreements, if any, with the Customers. All visitor information is collected along with any information that you volunteer as a customer while using Customers using our Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd’s Internet Banking.

Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd endeavours to safeguard and ensure the security of the information provided by the Customer. Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd uses advanced encryption of data, for the transmission of the information, which is currently the permitted level of encryption in India. When the information provided by the Customers is not transmitted through this encryption, the Customer’s system (if configured accordingly) will display an appropriate message ensuring the best level of secrecy for the Customer’s information.

The Customer would be required to cooperate with Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd in order to ensure the security of the information, and it is recommended that the Customers necessarily choose their passwords carefully such that no unauthorised access is made by a third party. To make the password complex and difficult for others to guess, the Customers should use combination of alphabets, numbers and special characters (like !, @, #, $ etc.). The Customers should undertake not to disclose their password to anyone or keep any written or other record of the password such that a third party could access it.

Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd undertakes not to disclose the information provided by the Customers to any person, unless such action is necessary to:

  * Protect and defend Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd’s or its Affiliate’s rights, interests or property;
  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process;
  * Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services; or
  * Act to protect the interests of Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons.

Customers shall not disclose to anyone, in any manner, any info, relating to TMB Ltd or its Affiliates, of a confidential nature obtained in the course of availing the services through the website. Failure to comply shall be deemed a serious breach of the terms herein and shall entitle TMB Ltd or its Affiliates to terminate the services, without prejudice to damages, to which the customer may be entitled otherwise.

Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd will limit the collection and use of customer information only on a need-to-know basis to deliver better service to the customers. Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd may use and share the information provided by the Customers with its Affiliates and third parties for providing services and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees for such services, and notifying or contacting the Customers regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary to disclose the customer information to one or more agents and contractors of Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd and their sub-contractors, but such agents, contractors, and sub-contractors will be required to agree to use the information obtained from Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd only for these purposes.

The Customer authorises Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd to exchange, share, part with all information related to the details and transaction history of the Customers to its Affiliates / banks / financial institutions / credit bureaus / agencies/participation in any telecommunication or electronic clearing network as may be required by law, customary practice, credit reporting, statistical analysis and credit scoring, verification or risk management and shall not hold Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd liable for use or disclosure of this information.

Children visiting Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd’s web site : We are confident that parents will not judge any of the information provided by Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd as objectionable for viewing by their children.
